{
  "extraDescription": "first operand is always divisible by second operand if second operand is not zero",
  "openingRemarks": "NB: You can enter 'U' or 'unexpected' for results which are not expected or defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "49 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "7",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "48 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "99 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "11",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "33 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "60 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "10",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "30 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "35 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "5",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "45 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "5",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "5",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "33 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "11",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "66 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "11",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "48 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "8",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "40 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "3",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "40 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "5",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "30 &#xF7; 3",
      "answer": "10",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "56 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "7",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "45 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "9",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "60 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "66 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "6",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "100 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "10",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "72 &#xF7; 9",
      "answer": "8",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "8",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "88 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "11",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "36 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "9",
      "expectedDenominators": [0]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [0],
      "answer": "2"
    }
  ]
}
